Michael Jacquemart

Web developer - Back-end

ADDRESS 60 rue des béguines, 4350 Momalle BELGIUM

PHONE +32 495 11 35 11

michaeljacquemart.webdev
@gmail.com

SOCIAL MEDIA

LINKEDIN

michael-jacquemart-85bbb2143

GITHUB

michaeljacquemart

Junior Web Developer specializing in back-end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Wellversed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, JavaScript, CSS3, MySQL, C, MATLAB and a bit of Python. Strong background in project management.

EDUCATION

2006 - 2012 O CESS

Athénée Royal de Waremme: MATH8/scientific.

2013 - 2018 © Engineering

University of Liège: Unfinished Bachelor in electricity and electronics.

2019 – may to december

Coding bootcamp

Becode.org: 7 months of web development.

EXPERIENCE

2013-14

Summers of O LAURENTY Rénovation

Building laborer: Floor tiling, prep work.

Summers of 2015-16

o Ethias

Accounting: Balances verification, differences justifications on Excelsheets (savings, insurance, etc.) and use of the Ethias Intranet. Excel study of customer histories: comparison of fees by region, type of customer, age, etc.

2019 O Becode.org

Junior web developer: Exercising in real situations and projects.